(gentle music)
♪ La, la, li, da, da, la, la ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Ah yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Don't leave me in all this pain ♪
♪ Don't leave me out in the rain ♪
♪ Come back and bring back my smile ♪
♪ Come and take these tears away ♪
♪ I need your arms to hold me now ♪
♪ The nights are so unkind ♪
♪ Bring back those nights
when I held you beside me ♪
♪ Unbreak my heart ♪
♪ Say you'll love me again ♪
♪ Undo this hurt you caused
when you walked out the door ♪
♪ And walked out of my life ♪
♪ Uncry these tears ♪
♪ I cried so many nights ♪
♪ Unbreak my heart ♪
♪ My heart ♪
♪ Take back that sad word goodbye ♪
♪ Bring back the joy to my life ♪
♪ Don't leave me here with these tears ♪
♪ Come and kiss this pain away ♪
♪ I can't forget the day you left ♪
♪ Time is so unkind ♪
♪ And life is so cruel
without you here beside me ♪
♪ Unbreak my heart ♪
♪ Say you'll love me again ♪
♪ Undo this hurt you caused
when you walked out the door ♪
♪ And walked out of my life ♪
♪ Uncry these tears ♪
♪ I cried so many nights ♪
♪ Unbreak my heart ♪
♪ Oh, ooh ♪
(sultry music)
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Don't leave me in all this pain ♪
♪ Don't leave me out in the rain ♪
♪ Bring back the nights
when I held you beside me ♪
♪ Unbreak my heart ♪
♪ Say you'll love me again ♪
♪ Undo this hurt you caused
when you walked out the door ♪
♪ And walked out of my life ♪
♪ Uncry these tears ♪
♪ I cried so many, many nights ♪
♪ Oh, unbreak my ♪
♪ Unbreak my heart, oh, baby ♪
♪ Come back and say you love me ♪
♪ Unbreak my heart, sweet darlin' ♪
♪ Without you I just can't go on ♪
♪ Can't go on ♪
♪ Whoo ♪
♪ Tell me you love me, unbreak my ♪
♪ Say that you love me,
say that you love me ♪
Tell me you love me, unbreak my
Say that you love me, say that you love me